The streets - your only chance for life.
Streetwise is a documentary film directed by Martin Bell.
This documentary about teenagers living on the streets
in Seattle began as a magazine article.
The film follows nine teenagers who discuss how they live by
panhandling, prostitution, and petty theft.
Self, played by Erin Blackwell.
Self, played by Dewayne Pomeroy.
Self, played by Roberta Joseph Hayes.
Self, played by Lulu Couch.
Self, played by Reed Early.
Self, played by Patrice Pitts.
Streetwise is a 1984 documentary film by director Martin Bell chronicling
the lives of homeless youth on the streets of Seattle.
It followed in the wake of a July 1983 Life magazine article "Streets of the Lost" by
writer Cheryl McCall and photographer Mary Ellen Mark (Bell's wife).
The film explores themes of seattle, washington, homelessness,
teenage prostitute, homeless, homeless teenager.